<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on dziopa.com</title>
    <link>https://dziopa.com/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on dziopa.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dziopa.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Izolacja? Dobry czas na naukę programowania!</title>
      <link>https://dziopa.com/post/2-izolacja/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 18:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dziopa.com/post/2-izolacja/</guid>
      <description>Długie dni w domu i niepewna sytuacja na rynku pracy Niepewność: to słowo ostatnio zyskało bardzo na popularności. Niepewność wkrada się w temat naszego zdrowia, stabilności finansowej, pracy i planów na przyszłość. Jedną z niewielu pewnych rzeczy jest to, że przez najbliższych kilka tygodni Twoja aktywność towarzyska, rekreacyjna, rozrywkowa i edukacyjna będzie mocno ograniczona przez samoizolację.
Ten czas to idealny moment, żeby zacząć naukę programowania! Poświęcając kilka godzin w tygodniu za jednym zamachem:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Natural Language Processing in Polish</title>
      <link>https://dziopa.com/post/1-getting-started-nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 18:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dziopa.com/post/1-getting-started-nlp/</guid>
      <description>There are countless tutorials on how to do NLP on the internet. Why would you care to read another one? Well, we will be looking into analysing Polish language, which is still rather underdeveloped in comparison to English.
Polish language is much more complex when compared to English language, as it contains 7 cases (deklinacja), 3 kinds (masculine, femenine, unspecified) and 11 different templates of verb conjugation, not to mention the exceptions [1] [2] [3].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>https://dziopa.com/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 18:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dziopa.com/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>This is the place where I will be sharing my thoughts and tinkering. Hope you will like it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>